ipqualityscore.com 2019-03-21

# Privacy Policy | IPQualityScore.com

_Last Revised Feb 9th, 2019_  
**IPQualityScore values your privacy and is fully compliant with GDPR regulations. All data shared with IPQualityScore is kept confidential and is never sold or made publicly available. Please also review ourData Processing Agreement for more details.**

IPQualityScore Privacy Policy Overview 

This Privacy Policy document outlines the privacy measures of IPQualityScore, LLC (referred to as "IPQualityScore", "IPQS", "we", or "us"), in relation to the IPQualityScore.com website (the "Website") and any features, products, and online services (referred to as "services") provided by IPQualityScore. IPQualityScore values the privacy of our visitors and users. This Privacy Policy details the types of data and information that we collect and how we safeguard this data. 

Our Services That Process Data 

IPQualityScore's primary service is focused on fraud detection and prevention. We may use data related to you to analyze transactions, registrations, clicks, and other user behavior to determine if the intent is malicious or fraudulent. IPQualityScore's machine learning algorithms and data processing mechanisms are designed with this privacy framework in mind to prevent data leakage and protect your rights to privacy. 

Web Server Log Files 

Like most web sites, IPQualityScore makes use of log files through our web server. This data includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and timestamps, referring & exit pages, and clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. Each of these data points is not personally identifiable on its own. 

Scripts, Cookies, and Web Beacons 

IPQualityScore may use cookies, pixel tags, embedded scripts, web beacons and similar technologies to store information about visitor preferences, record user behavior and actions, customize services based on the visitor's browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

Information & Data Collection 

**Personal Information** : information that identifies you as an individual or relates to an identifiable individual, including: name, unique identifier (such as account ID), email address, physical address, telephone number, credit card information, geolocation, and IP address. If you submit any Personal Information relating to other people to us or to our service providers in connection with our services, you represent that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**Non-Personal Information** : any information that does not directly reveal your specific identity or does not directly relate to an identifiable individual. This might include pseudonymous identifiers and information, device information, non-precise geolocation, information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies, and web server log files to track trends, administer the Website, track user movement, and gather demographic information. 

IPQualityScore does not collect more information than is necessary to provide accurate fraud detection services. 

Data Sharing & Data Processing 

Clients using our service may provide IPQualityScore with transactional information, which may include IP addresses, email addresses, billing details, phone numbers, and similar user data. This information is processed through our services to detect behavioral intent and analyze the risk profile of transactions and users. This data is used to identify patterns of fraud within our system and improve your account's personal machine learning algorithms. 

IPQualityScore will **NEVER** sell or make publicly available any of your account's data or transaction/user information that is processed via our APIs or tools. Any data shared with IPQualityScore will be kept confidential, secured, and stored in the safest manner above industry standards. 

Data Processing Agreement 

Please review our full Data Processing Agreement for more details on how we handle personal data while respecting relevant privacy laws including the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). 

Data Security 

IPQualityScore takes reasonable measures to protect all data collected from unauthorized access, breaches, loss, manipulation, falsification, destruction or unauthorized disclosure. 

Your Privacy Rights & Access to Information 

You have the right to request access to any personal information we may have collected for you. IPQualityScore can provide a copy of your stored personal data. In order to comply with your request, we may ask you to verify your identity. Please contact us at [Support@IPQualityScore.com](mailto:S%75p%70or%74@IP%51uality%53c%6Fre%2Ecom) to submit a personal information request. 

Information Correction & Deletion 

If you believe that the information we have recorded about you is incorrect, you are welcome to contact us so we can update it and keep your data accurate. You also have the right to request that we delete any information about you. In order to comply with your request, we may ask you to verify your identity. Please contact us at [Support@IPQualityScore.com](mailto:S%75p%70or%74@IP%51uality%53c%6Fre%2Ecom) to submit an information deletion request. 

Data Compliance Officer 

Should you have any questions related to your privacy or would like to speak with our Data Compliance Officer, please use the contact information below.

ATTN: Data Compliance Officer  
IPQualityScore LLC  
PO Box 19052  
Las Vegas, Nevada 89132  
USA  

Summary 

IPQualityScore takes every precaution to safeguard your data. We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time as we constantly improve our policies. 

If you require more details or have any questions concerning our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us.
